I can tell you about her.
I can tell you everything
I know about this place.
I don't know if you'll believe
me, but it's worth a shot.
Go on, then.
However, if I detect even a trace of deceit
in your words, I shall end your life.
I'm going to break your time.
I'm going to be ready for the time.
I'm not going to have
to break up the window.
Now, let's break out any
of the power of this.
I'm going to have a strong feeling.
And the heart of this dream
is not going to change it.
We don't have any pain.
See
you
next time.
What are you doing?
I knew I'd find you boys goofing off.
Tonkii it.
Oh, hi, Alice.
Did your sacred arts
class let out early today?
Because, like, you're Integrity
Knight Alice Synthesis 30.
I'm not early at all.
But your real name is Alice Zuburg.
Your dad's the elder of Real.
I heard you were good at sacred
arts and cooking as a kid.
Alice, your cooking keeps
getting better. For real.
Oh, I don't know.
It turned out okay, I guess.
But it could have been better.
Eight years ago,
you and this boy who was
your best friend went to
the End Mountains to get
some ice for your village.
On the way out, you took the wrong tunnel.
There it is!
Where are we?
The Dark Territory.
You came out where the Taboo
Index forbids everyone from going.
The Dark Territory.
No, wait!
Alice!
All you did was touch the ground in the
Dark Territory with your fingertips.
But no one can violate the Taboo Index.
Not even by mistake.
Your daughter, Alice Zuburg,
has disobeyed the Taboo Index.
I shall take her with me to answer
for her crimes and be executed.
Don't just stand there! Go help her!
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Get these guys off me!
Come on, hurry!
Yu-Gi-Oh!
You were taken to Senator by an
Integrity Knight called Tiese Elbert.
No one knew what happened
to you after that.
Alice! Yes!
Well, actually, someone used to bring me
my lunch every day, but that was years ago.
Oh, well.
So why'd they stop?
She was my childhood friend.
She was the same age as me.
When we were little, we
played together all the time.
And after I received my calling, she would
bring me lunch every day without fail.
But then, because of me...
That boy who was your best
friend, his name's Eugeo,
and his calling was to
cut down the Giga Cedar.
It was his idea to find you
and bring you back to Rulid.
I'm scared.
What?
I can't just stand here.
I can't make the same
mistake I made with Alice.
When Tiese Elbrick came to take you,
Eugeo wanted to stop him, but he froze.
The guilt's been eating
away at him ever since.
Die!
Get him down!
It's time!
I'll fight!
And protect my friends!
Run, Yu-Gi-Oh!
Yu-Gi-Oh!
Hang on, Yu-Gi-Oh! Please!
We made a promise.
You, me, and Alice.
We promised we'd protect each other.
I couldn't six years ago.
But now, finally, I got to.
Eugeo figured if he was going to bring
you back home, he'd have to get stronger.
So he decided to be a swordsman.
Hey, look it! And what?
After seven years of chopping away at the
Giga Cedar, Eugeo had finally cut it down.
That's how he got to pick
swordsmen for his new calling.
Well then, are you ready?
Uh-huh.
He left Rulid for Senator,
and I went with him.
It took a while, but we got
into the Swordcraft Academy.
We had good mentors there,
and learned a ton from them.
Academy right here.
The plan was to become Integrity Knights.
Get inside the Central
Cathedral, find you, and bring you home.
First things first, though.
We have to ace this exam.
Only the top 12 will get to advance.
After we became Elite
Disciples, we had to deal with
something we weren't prepared for.
Eugeo's page, Tise, and my page, Ronie.
They were taken taken prisoner by two
bastards from noble families, Umber and Rios.
Yu-Gi-Oh went to their room to
confront them and save the girls.
Such is my sovereign right!
Stop your squirming and take your punishment
like a good girl. Leave him alone!
Hold your ground, commoner!
Rios ordered Yu-Gi-Oh not to move,
And he was frozen on the spot.
He had to stand there and watch
as those two assaulted the girls.
And the only reason he
was powerless to help?
Was because the Taboo Index says commoners
have to obey a nobleman's orders.
It's a stupid law that's planted in the
souls of every person in the human empire.
No one can defy it.
If upholding laws like
these is my duty, then...
And then I...
I...
What's going on?
Wait, this happened before.
This is evil.
I have to...
Stop them!
Help us! Please!
Yen-Yen!
Instead of standing there helpless,
and obeying the taboo index, laws that
kept him from saving people he cared about?
He chose to do what's
right and fought back.
That piece of junk will shatter
against my secret technique!
We'll see about that!
Well now, how is that?
You can't possibly have thought I,
Royos Antinus, would struggle
against a pissant like you!
Kirito...
I cut Rios' arms off, because
I was protecting Eugeo.
But the Taboo Index X forbids
killing another human,
or even taking part in their death.
So, Yu-Gi-Oh and I were arrested.
I am the Integrity Knight who
oversees the capital of Senator.
I am Alice Synthesis 30.
Alice, it's you, isn't it?
In a weird twist of fate, the Integrity
Knight they sent to arrest us was you.
I was kind of shocked.
You were nothing like the girl
Eugeo was always talking about.
You are in violation of the Taboo Index.
I will take you into custody, then
question you, then execute you.
You've only been here
for a day and a half.
After that, you tossed us in
the Central Cathedral's dungeon.
Then we broke out and came face to face
with another Integrity Knight, Eldriang.
System call.
Enhance armament.
Don't sweat it.
A whip can only reach so far.
We're safe here.
Release Recollection.
And fighting him, we got a taste of the
secret skills of you Integrity Knights.
Perfect weapon control and memory release.
No wonder Lady Alice was wary of you.
Your attacks have no pattern, which
is surprising and slightly irritating.
The only way we survived
Eldrie is because we
stumbled on another secret
of the Integrity Knights.
What's that?
I bet Alice got one of those, too, when
they blocked her memory and changed her.
But then, Tiese Elbert showed up, and
we had to get the hell out of there.
Attempting an Integrity Knight to fall
from grace is unforgivable, you wretches.
I shall pin you down, then
return you to your cell.
This way!
Dead end up ahead!
What do we do?
Hey!
Over here!
Follow her.
Where are we?
Now they know we're here.
We can't use this back door anymore.
We'd be dead if it wasn't for Cardinal.
She's the caretaker of the Great Library.
She's the one who told me all
the secrets of this world.
Thank you.
Come with me.
I'll try to be as succinct as possible.
System call.
Generate luminous element.
Form element. Liquid shape.
She told about how a simple girl
named Quinella became administrator,
the pontifex of the Axiom Church.
Through the Synthesis Ritual,
this man will be reborn as a
warrior devoted only to me,
my Integrity Knight.
She also told me how
you knights are made by
sealing away your memories
and planting fake ones.
And how do I do that?
Simply remove the piety module.
All the knights have
one in their forehead.
When Eugeo had a chance to ask her something,
he asked how to get your memory back.
And then, to get to you,
we had to fight our way through
a bunch of Integrity Knights.
No bear!
I can't...
Don't worry, I won't kill you.
I'm gonna teach you a lesson today.
You're gonna watch these
knights you made fun
of fight and see what
real strength's all about.
You didn't come this far because you
hated the Integrity Knights, did you?
You're here to get Alice back.
You're here because you love her.
But guess what?
That Integrity Knight, she feels
just as strong about her duty.
And I'm no different.
I want to protect everyone in this world.
You, Alice, even this night.
We're so close, and we
can't afford to give up now.
Ain't that right, Yu-Gi-Oh?
We made it all the way up to the 80th
floor, and that's where we found you.
I shall eliminate you.
Enhance armaments!
He went for my sword!
We thought we had a good plan, but
you were stronger than the both of us.
Now here we are, on the
wall outside the cathedral.
Ha, ha, ha.
Come and get it, kid.
I bet Eugeo's fighting his way
up right now, looking for you.
Blue Rose Sword, lend me your power!
Release Recollection!
That's it, but there's one
last thing I have to tell you.
Soon, everything in this world
is going to come to an end.
Cardinal told me it's about to enter its
final phase, and there's no stopping it.
The day when the Dark Territory
invades the human empire.
Cardinal's job is to make sure
there's balance in this world,
and she told me she
didn't accept its fate.
She believes the only way to
restore balance to the underworld
now is to wipe the slate clean
and return it to nothing.
So this is it.
Now I see this is what
it means to be human.
To be held.
It's so warm and comforting.
After 200 years.
This makes the wait worth it.
To think something so simple!
Could be so satisfying.
The wait was more than worth it.
She's not looking forward
to what she has to do.
She's got a heart.
I know that.
System call I told her
that once we made it
through the nights and
took administrator down.
Once and for all I'd figure out a way to
save this world and all the people in it.
That's pretty much everything I
know and what I know to be true.
You can believe it or not!
If you do and you want
to save this world and?
everyone in it.
I could sure use your help, Alice.
The world is so hard to live.
I can't walk.
I want to be loved.
I can't be loved. I can't be loved.
I can't be loved.
Life goes on.
Oh, everything turns to ash to ash.
And everything turns to dust to dust.
So give me no more?
Next time, the seal of the right eye.